https://www.horizontechnology.com/privacy-policy/

MenuITADReviewRefreshReuseReturnRecycleStorageHard DrivesProcurementData SanitizationProfessional ServicesCompanyAbout UsHorizon HelpsCertificationsOur MissionResourcesHorizon BlogStorage Market BriefsCase StudiesITAD GlossaryDecommissioning ChecklistContact Us
ITAD
Review
Refresh
Reuse
Return
Recycle
Storage
Hard Drives
PRIVACY POLICY
Horizon Technology understands that you care about how your information is used and shared; we value the trust you put in us to keep your information safe and we will continue to respect the privacy of our users.
This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website https://horizontechnology.com including any other media form, media channel, mobile website, or web application related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Horizon Technology”).
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE SITE.
We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will mark any changes by updating the “Revised” date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification.
You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of Horizon Technology after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.
Collection Of Your Information
We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on the Site includes:
Personal Data
Personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, telephone number, shipping address, and demographic information, such as your age that you voluntarily give to us when you register with the Site or when you choose to participate in various activities related to the Site, such as online chat and form fills. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind. However, your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Site.
Derivative Data
Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Site, such as your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the pages you have viewed directly before and after accessing the Site.
Use of Your Information
Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. Specifically, we may use information collected about you via the Site and App to:
Send you a newsletter
Create and manage your account
Notify you of updates to the site
Perform other business activities as needed
Monitor and analyze usage and trends to improve your experience with the Site
Increase the efficiency and operation of the Site
Email you regarding your account or order
Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties
Disclosure of Your Information
All user information (including information collected by usage) is not shared outside of the Horizon Technology ecosystem. Your information may only be disclosed as follows:
By Law or to Protect Rights
If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation.  This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Affiliates
We do not share your user information with our affiliates. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.
Tracking Technologies
Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customize the Site and improve your experience.
Website Analytics
We may also partner with selected third-party vendors, such as to allow tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Site through the use of first party cookies and third-party cookies, to, among other things, analyze and track users’ use of the Site, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity.
By accessing the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by these third-party vendors. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. We do not transfer personal information to these third-party vendors. However, If you do not want any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, you can visit the third-party vendor or the Network Advertising Initiative or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool.
We do not provide any Personal Information to an advertiser when you interact with or view a customized advertisement. However, when you view or interact with an advertisement, the possibility exists that the advertiser will make the assumption that you are interested in the subject matter of the advertisements.
You should be aware that getting a new computer, installing a new browser, upgrading an existing browser, or erasing or otherwise altering your browser’s cookies files may also clear certain opt-out cookies, plug-ins, or settings.
Third-Party Websites
The Site may contain links to third-party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of your information.
Before visiting and providing any information to any third-party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect the privacy of your information.
We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other sites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Site.
Security of Your Information
We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information.
While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.
Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information.
Controls for Do-Not-Track Features
Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected.
No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online.
If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy.
Emails and Communications
If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-out by emailing:
marketing@horizontechnology.com
or use any opt-out option available within the communication.
If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.
California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year.
If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below. If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Site, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Site.
To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California.  We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Site, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.
Contact Us
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
Horizon Technology
Attn: Privacy Inquiry
1 Rancho Circle
Lake Forest, CA, 92630
United States
(949) 454-4600
+1 (949)-595-8244
sales@horizontechnology.com
info@horizontechnology.com
HORIZON Horizon is your trusted resource for IT asset recovery in the data center. We return value to your IT budget and bottom line.
Find out more about Horizon.
COMPANY INFO Contact
About
Privacy Policy
Certifications
RESOURCES Horizon Blog
ITAD Glossary
Case Studies
Storage Market Briefs
FOLLOW US Twitter
LinkedIn
© 2019 Horizon Technology - Data Center ITAD & Storage Remarketing
MenuITADReviewRefreshReuseReturnRecycleStorageHard DrivesProcurementData SanitizationProfessional ServicesCompanyAbout UsHorizon HelpsCertificationsOur MissionResourcesHorizon BlogStorage Market BriefsCase StudiesITAD GlossaryDecommissioning ChecklistContact Us
